socialcash.com 2014-04-21

# Spruce Media » Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to the use of [sprucemedia.com](http://sprucemedia.com/) and our advertising management software and services. We highly value the privacy of our clients and their customers and make this policy available throughout our site.

This Privacy Policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. By proceeding to use our service, you consent that we may process the personal data (including potentially sensitive personal data) that we collect from you in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and contact us if you have any questions. You may contact us by mail at the following address:

Controller  
Spruce Media  
500 3rd Street Suite 245  
San Francisco, CA 94107  

### Activity Logs and Cookies

Spruce Media utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, computer operating system and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual people; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage. Cookies may also be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or returning visits. Cookies are small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. We do not link the information stored in cookies to any personally identifiable information you have submitted while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when your browser is closed, and a persistent cookie may stay on your hard drive for an extended period. Session cookies make it easier for you to navigate our site; persistent cookies can perform such activities as storing your password so you do not have to sign in every time you visit those areas, and/or may be used to enable us to track and target the behavior of our users so as to enhance the overall experience of using our site.

In addition, Spruce Media uses cookies in connection with consumers visiting the web pages of our clients to whom we provide services. The data we collect in connection with consumers is used solely for tracking clicks and web events – and is not used for any multiple-site data collection. You can manage or disable cookies through tools provided with your web browser software and with third-party software packages.

We have no access to or administration abilities over any cookies that are used by our advertising clients or partners.

### Links to other Websites or Applications

[Sprucemedia.com](http://sprucemedia.com/), our advertising management software and services may contain links to applications or other sites such as news outlets, commerce sites or web services that are not controlled in any way by Spruce Media. We are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website or property other than our own. Spruce Media strongly suggests that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit.

### Registration and Use of Personal Information

Registration is not required in order to use or access [sprucemedia.com](http://sprucemedia.com/). If you do register for one of our services or email lists, and in the process provide us with personally identifiable information, rest assured that any such information you provide will not proactively be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.

We may provide visitors to our website the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. In this case, we ask the visitor for his or her email address and name. These communications may include our standard newsletter, product promotions and any other information that we feel may be relevant to the registrant. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications by emailing or writing us at the contact information made available at the end of this document.

### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer wish us to possess your information, you may request correction, updating, or deletion of your information by emailing or writing us at the contact information made available at the end of this document.

### Security

We follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to us. However, please be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be 100% secure. Therefore, as is the case with any organization – we are not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information.

We use reasonable measures to protect user information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. As noted, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. 

You may submit any questions you may have about our security procedures by emailing or writing us at the contact information made available at the end of this document.

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our website.

### Change of Control

Spruce Media reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Spruce Media or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the “Changes in Our Privacy Policy” section below.

### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

Spruce Media reserves the right to make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so they will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A user is bound by any minor changes to the policy when he or she uses the site after those changes have been posted. If we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

### Contact Details

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or you wish to contact us by postal mail, our contact information is as follows:

Controller  
Spruce Media  
500 3rd Street Suite 245  
San Francisco, CA 94107
